upfront group
Here we go... Up God!
This time I'll be talking with Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 23's Ayumi Ishida and
Saori Onoda of Tsuboki Factory.
This show will take you behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the up-front group.
This is a program that goes behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Upfront Group.
Our recording, rehearsal, and other production processes.
We will show you the process of our recording and rehearsal.
First of all, let's take a look behind the scenes of our two MC's. I, Ishida, was at the Nippon Budokan for Morning Musume。 23 spring tour at Nippon Budokan,
In the spring, we performed the song "Here I am" at the very end of the tour.
And of course we were going to sing it at the Budokan as well, so I wondered how the seniors would feel about Morning Musume。 I was wondering how the seniors had performed "Here I am" and I was looking for the past videos.
In that search, I came across a video of Tsunku III singing "Koko ni iruze" on youtube,
When I saw Tsunku III singing "Here I am," I felt that I was able to absorb more of the rhythms and nuances of his singing now than I had when I saw him sing it in the past,
I was very happy to see the changes in myself, and I was able to notice that my feelings toward rhythm have changed, even if only a little, which was a very pleasant discovery recently.
I see. It is wonderful to be able to make good changes, isn't it?
I would like to deepen my learning so that I can have the same kind of conversation three years from now.
I, Onoda, have recently had many opportunities to perform as Tsubaki Factory at outdoor summer festivals, and I am very happy to be able to do so,
I have often had the opportunity to see other artists perform at summer festivals, and many of the members have been inspired by their performances,
That is one of the reasons why I would like to continue to develop my passion and enthusiasm for summer festivals,
We have an open-air concert called "Burning Live" on August 24th,
Tsubaki's solo concert.
Yes, that's right. I would like to work hard for that outdoor concert.
There is definitely a kind of heat that only summer can bring, isn't there?
Yes, there is.
There is heat and we have our own heat, so we want to do our best while enjoying both.
We are looking forward to seeing Tsubaki Factory in summer.
Let's start with this up-date.
Ochanoma: A Little Emotionally Unstable Summer - Making of the Music Video Shooting
Please take a look at the making of the music video for "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer" from Ochanoma's newest single to be released on July 26th.
Is it because of the summer? Whose fault is it?
Slightly Emotionally Unstable
Today, we are shooting the music video for "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer," the third single from Ochanoma.Today we are shooting a music video for Ochanoma's 3rd single, "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer".
Today was the first time for me to do something called hair arrangement for a music video,
It's our 3rd single, and I'm feeling a bit like a beginner,
I'm a little nervous,
I'm a little nervous, but to be frank, the theme of the music video is summer.
I just turned 17 years old,
I want to do my best to give it a high school feel.
I'm seriously dazzled.
I don't know what to do.
If I look up, I'll be in trouble.
Please, I'm begging you.
Is it the summer?
Whose fault is it?
A little unstable.
I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying, I'm trying.
I'm six centimeters off the Earth.
I thought I was dressed up, but I'm not.
My ideal type is different from you
A collage of emotions, a reverb of love
A wave of passion, a heated garb.
I wonder if it's the summer, or if it's a dream, or if I'm just a little unstable.
I wonder whose fault it is, you wonder if it's yours, I'm not sure who it is
Travel is a dance band Fireworks are a band It's the end of the season
Girls collaborate Summer's in the air, whimsical, changing seven ways
A little emotionally unstable
This song is called "Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer.
The lyrics were written by Ms. Kamie Hirose!
This song was composed by a very famous artist and Ms. Kami Hirose.
It was the first time I had ever heard a summer song with a tea cup.
I was so excited to hear it.
I think it's a very fun song to listen to.
Please give it a listen!Please listen to it!
Thank you very much.
Kiralyn
Thank you for your time
Bye bye
🐥
waffle
I'm a little unstable.
I'm a little unstable emotionally,
We are going to shoot a music video in the summer, but it's going to be in a place where you can feel the summer,
We are shooting in a place where you can feel the summer,
The members are very excited about it.
We are wearing swimsuits for the shoot.
I'm not sure who you are.
The summer sun is in the air, fireworks are in the air, and it's the season of summer.
and it's the season of the hatena!
With a girl, it's a summer tiger
whimsy, whimsy, seven changes
A little emotional instability Summer
Dameyoka?
Wow! Gross!
Se-no!
Mince, mince, mince.
Cut!
Oh, I found a toy for you!
Here's Masyu.
Is it a dream? Hey, hey, hey!
This is the last guest of this year.
It's been so hot, but it's still hot,
It's still hot,
From the Moose Office in Slote, I'm going to show you my
The largest in 23 directions!Largest in 23 directions!
7th Street!
Just Ok!
I'm so happy!
Thank you so much!
Thank you very much!
That's it!
Today we shot a little bit unstable summer music video,
The music video is filled with various summer elements such as swimming pools and fireworks,
We hope you will watch it again and again.
Now that you have seen the VTR, I was thinking about it when I saw the music video, but I thought the way the Ochanooma members did so many cute hand gestures during the lip scene, which is unique to teenagers, was really cute.
The way they were all so determined.
I got the impression that the scenes where they are not singing are also very young, with a kind of "hmmm" feeling, which is a charm that only today's Ochanomama can bring out.
Yes, that's right. I could feel the fun in the making of the video, not only in the music video, but also during the filming, which made me enjoy watching it,
I could feel that they were having fun not only during the shoot, but also during the filming, which made me feel like I was having a lot of fun watching them.
It is true that the colors of the group have come through.
I am really looking forward to seeing more of the "Ocha-no-Oma" style in the future.
This is the making of the shooting of the music video for "Ochanoma Slightly Emotionally Unstable Summer".
me
Nakakazu Funky Prossie, I'll press your name.
I had a good thing happen today.
BGM
Next up, here's Angulum's Ai no Kedamono Vocalo Recording
From Angulum's latest single, Ai no Kedamono, here's a look at Rikako Sasaki's vocalo recording.
It's totally a song about a carnivorous girl. That's right.
It's like a cheetah that's hunting its prey.
Let's start with Emel. I like to be independent, so I'm not going to go that far.
Let's go for it.I'll tell you what.
People ask me what I like about you, but in the end, I'm not kidding.
It's not the kind of love that makes you withdraw after three days and three nights of worrying about it.
Yes, yes, it's nice. Well, a little bit, just a little bit, but something like...
Not like a nikko, but like a niyah, like a little bit of a wheyim.
Yes, yes.
Let's write it like that.
Yes.
Ui.
People ask me what I like about him, but in the end, it's not a gut feeling.
It's not the kind of love that makes you withdraw after three days and three nights of worrying about it.
Live for love. You're putting your life on the line.
I won't hide it anymore, you're my target, and I'm sure your way of life is beautiful.
I don't have time to be shy.
It's a way of life.
That's the way to live.
Don't let it go down the drain.
Such a way of life...
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Now we just need to start with you in front of the target.
I'm not gonna hide it anymore, you're the target
You're the target.
I can't help but think of the next "you're the target.
I like the "no" part.
It's like, "No more hiding.
Let's try it again.
Live for love. You're risking your life for love.
I'm not gonna hide it anymore... you're the target... and that's a beautiful way to live.
I don't want to be shy.
Okay.
Okay, now the chorus.All right, so we'll start with the chorus.
There's a high part like "If you love me, I'll introduce you...
Rather than trying to hit the right notes there, too.
I think it's better to just go for it with a bang.
Let's go for longevity.
Please do.
If we love you, we'll say it.
The earth is a place where the law of the jungle is the law of the jungle.
Breathe in, breathe out, and if your eyes meet mine...
See? I'm already hooked.
I love you
I've already figured out how I'm going to get on with the melody, so all that's left is to see if I can get on with the music.
Now it's just a matter of whether or not I can get on board with the music.
If you can't get the high notes, you can't listen to the music properly, so I think it's a little bit difficult.
If you can do your best to listen to the music, I think you'll be fine.
Okay.
Okay, let's go!
I love you!
When we love you, we say it
We are the weak and the strong on earth
When you feel my breath and our eyes meet
See, we're already hooked
Okay, okay.
Well, I guess it's a little soul-crushing.
But it's great.
It's totally fine, it's totally fine, it's totally fine.
See, I'm into it now.
We're in love, we're in love, we're in love, we're in love
Our fiery encounters are on the verge of extinction
I'll protect you, won't I?
I'll protect you so much, won't I?
Okay, okay, I've already written the first three lines, so this is totally fine.Yes, yes, yes, the first three lines are already perfect, so this is totally fine.
I'll protect you very much, won't I?
I'll give you the first three lines now.
It's just a matter of how quickly you decide on this part.
Yes, sir.
I'm going to concentrate on that one line.
One line?
Just that one line.
I'll protect you very much.
That's it. - Okay.
Okay.
I'm gonna protect you.
I'll protect you so much.
Okay, then, really feel how strong you really are. Let's try this.
Just really, really feel it. Just try it like that.
Yes.
And then, in the same vein, we did "Ai no Dekimono. This one is also called "Ai no Dekimono.
Oh. Yes.
Yes. Just, uh, look at what you want to listen to like that.
Yes. Let's go.
Feel it.
The beast of love. Be ready for it.
Last one says, "Be ready.
Which one is round?
"Be prepared.
I think I'd rather throw a dang dang dang dang dang dang dang dang dang dang dang dang
Tah-tah-tah?
Yeah.
I'm gonna protect you so much, aren't I?
You should really feel how strong I am.
You're a beast of love. Prepare yourself.
I thought I could feel your power in the recording.I could feel your power in the recording video.
Recording is not a performance, it's just recording the song.
But even in that state, I felt that it must be very difficult to control your breathing and the amount of breath you take.
But on top of that, when you perform, you have to dance.
But you also look so wonderful when you dance and sing.
I could feel what I respect about Ms. Sasaki even more.
I was reminded once again how wonderful you are when you perform.
Recording is like recording a whole song.
But when it comes to the actual song, the parts are divided and only this part is sung.
But Rikako sings from the previous phrase and then sings the next phrase, and that kind of way of filming is very clear.
I felt that even if she sings only this part, she must be a girl who can sing with the whole song in mind.
That was the vocal recording of Rikako Sasaki, the beast of Angstrom's love.
Cheer up!
Okay, first of all, let's see how you play it.
If it doesn't sound good enough, let's try a little EQ.
If you don't mind.
I'm fine, thank you.
Listen to this.
I've got a shell of Khamsir here.
At my fingertips.
I'm a boring cog in a boring wheel.
I'm going to tell you
I'm so ashamed of myself
The birds I couldn't hear
And fly a lot more
Thank you for watching!
Sound Hodori 🐯 Sound Hodori 사운드 호돌이
Illustration Live trio Music Colors
Subscribe to our channel hesitate to do
It's about time to take me away
continue 7 minutes ahead
Back start nowNow back start.
You can be my girlfriend.
I'll be your true love.
Look, look, look. Petals from the window.
That's not the information I just gave you.
Hmm.
It's going up and up and up. Can I have another ten or so?
I'd love to. Are you sure this is a good place for basics?
Yes, I think so. Let's start from here.
It's the A-melody of a plain song. It would be nice if there was a phrase in the 27th bar.
Not stopping at the high F.
Yes, it would be nice if you said something.
Let's start with the A8, where you want to add that phrase.
Let's go with that.
Thank you very much.
Let's move on.
The second bead.
Kirakira, ai no sakurazakura, ai no sakurazakura, soon!
Perfect!
Thank you!
Then let me go to the next section!
I hate obvious love.
I'll be your girlfriend if you fall in love and spill it
I can't help it, I'm drowning in the sun
If I fall in love and spill it, I can't help it, I'll drown in the sun
It seems to be all right here.
Grease in front of the west?
Yes, sir.
Duin.
Duin.Doin' it!
Not in time!
Yes!
Awwwww!
But that's what timing is for!
OK, now it's done.
Then the second step of 3C.
Hmmm, let me get busy.
It's gonna be tricky.
I think I can do it, to be honest.
I'll be back here.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, okay.
We'll have to drop it once and come back.
You don't have to go back so hard.
It's all really nuanced now.
Just a little bit.
Oh, I'll lose it again.
I'll lose fingers again.
I'll do my best.
Autumn and winter, we're crossing paths, and I finally realize...
I want to stop, I can't wait, be her, love...
Oh, oh, oh. I think we're done.
I guess we're done then.
Okay, we're done. Thank you very much.
My name is Hideki Nagamatsu, I play the electric bass.
Yes, this song has a fast tempo.
Rather than playing 8 minutes of "da-da-da-da-da"...
The 16th minute of this song was very important to me, so I had to play it in a different way.
So I made sure to play the 16 minutes in the right way.
The song also has a beautiful melody.
I made the bass line so that it wouldn't interfere with the song.I made a bass line so as not to disturb the song.
In the latter half of the song, I tried to make a phrase that is a little difficult to play.
It's not a challenge, but I did it in my own way.
First of all, I used a bass phrase in the A melody, which is related to the vocalist's voice.
There is a bass phrase in the A-melody that is related to the vocalist, and there is a lot of movement at the end of the song.
You might think it's too much, but I'm glad you enjoyed it.
I hope you enjoy it as well.
My name is Koga, and I was in charge of the music composition and arrangement.
It's fresh and catchy, but in fact, there are a lot of modulations and technical parts.
The arrangement is a little bit like Tsubaki, a little bit like Tsubaki Factory, a little bit like spring, with a sense of speed.
For the bass, I wanted it to sing, and I wanted it to play as if it were singing.
As for the guitar, I wanted it to be fast and furious, but at the same time, the lyrics are quite sad, so I asked the guitarist to incorporate that sadness into the melody and tone of the guitar.
The whole song has a lot of modulations, and you can feel the girl's emotions change along with the modulations, which is really great.
As you have seen in the bass recording, the song "Seventh Bloom Continues" is a song about a girl's sad and true feelings that she wants to say but can't. It is a song about the feelings that she hides in her heart.
It's a song about a girl's sad and hidden feelings that she really wants to say but can't. It's a perfect song for spring.
I can actually hear the bass sound in the chorus and the interlude. When I play live, I can hear the bass sound. So I think it is wonderful to hear only the bass, and it is also fun to hear the bass in the song, so I really like the way the bass matches the song.
I really like how you played the bass guitar as if you were singing at the end of the song, and I could really understand the melody line by listening to just the bass guitar.
I thought it was really comfortable and cool to listen to the bass, and the part where the chorus falls at the end and the excitement builds up once more... it's really cool!
The left hand! The left hand! It was amazing!
So fast! There was a great climax of the song.
It's true that the chorus after the fall chorus in the song is really made to get the audience excited.
When we perform, we always try to make the performance more exciting.
All the various instruments are working towards that goal.
So I could feel more than ever that everyone was really working together on the song.
It was so much fun! It was a lot of fun!
That's all for the bass recording of Tsubaki Factory Shichibunsaki!
Shenkena!
The power of self-belief
Ordinary but forbidding
Chachanoma new single
Shekenare!
January 26th release!January 26th release!
Let's work together!
It's time for a deep farewell from Ayumi Ishida and Saori Onoda.
We have seen various videos this time, but I, Onoda, saw the making-of video of the shooting of the music video for "Tea Horse.
I saw the making of the music video of Ocha-no-Ma, and I felt that the character of Ocha-no-Ma was very wonderful.
I hope that Tsubaki Factory will be able to bring out more of the Tsubaki Factory's character.
I, Ishida, really enjoyed watching the recording of Tsubaki Factory's songs with the bass player.
But I've never seen Morning Musume。 But to be honest, there are not many times when the instrumental recordings of Morning Musume。
That's why I wanted to make it more interesting for the viewers.
In this Up-Kami, we will go behind the scenes of the production of various artists belonging to the Up-Front Group.
We'll introduce you to the parts you don't normally get to see, so please subscribe to our channel!
This time upcami will be with Ayumi Ishida of Morning Musume。 23's Ayumi Ishida and Tsubaki Factory's Saori Onoda.
Good bye.
Next time on UPKAMI
Ochanoma Shekenare Dance Lesson
And
Juice-Juice Drive Bright recording session!
Enjoy!
Please subscribe to our channel!